This won't take a minute.
用不了多久的.
No problem.I need stamps anyway.
没关系. 反正我也要买一些邮票.
Look.Here's the visa for my trip.
看. 这是我的签证.
Wow.Look at all the stamps.
WOW.盖了这么多章!
Yeah.I travelled so much in my previous job.
Yeah.我做前一份工作时常常要出差.
You worked with the Continental Hotel,right?
你过去在Continental Hotel工作,right?
Uh huh.I worked there from 1986 to 1989.
Uh huh.从1986年到1989年,我在那儿工作.
Indonesia.Argentina.Madagascar!
印度尼西亚. 阿根廷. 马达加斯加!
You should see my old passport.
你应该看看我们的旧护照.
I was in graduate school in Europe from'80 to'82.
1980年到1982年我在欧洲读研究生.
I went everywhere.
我到处都走遍了.
Terrible picture.
照片太糟糕了.
I know.
Your full name is Anne Bruce Holland?Bruce is a man's name.
你的全名是Anne Bruce Holland? Bruce是男人的名字.
It's family name.
这是家族的姓.
Place of birth:Connecticut,U.S.A.
出生地:Connecticut,U.S.A.
Hey,you were born on February 14th,1952.Valentine's Day.
Hey,你出生于1952年2月14日, 情人节!
Julia.You're holding up the line.
Julia.你挡住往前的队伍了.